Cineva a spus cândva:
„Iubirea este
„Iubirea este...
sursa de putere a unei fete.”
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
The sweet desire I found is here today as well
From inside of me
Someone screams at you to notice
We stare at one another, at an irritating distance
Alone, I endure
The onslaught of sadness
Though I want to tell you this feeling of love
I can't say a word
Though you're always at my side
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
A strong emotion set aflame
Nu voi ezita și nici nu vreau să ezit
I'll believe in now, and take a step forward
Pentru binele meu
U-Un iubit?!
N-Nu cred că sunt pregătită să am unul...
Ce ar trebui să facă o liceană dacă nu să se îndrăgostească?
Invigorating Drives
Social Observations
A Walk Around the City
Power Spots
Special Support for a Couple's Outing
Where will you go for today's date?
Iubirea e sursa de putere a unei fete, știi?
Natsuki chiar e grozavă.
E frumoasă precum o păpușă, are o inimă pură și interacționează la fel cu toată lumea...
E un adevărat înger!
Am auzit că o altă școală au creat un fanclub pentru ea.
E destul de evident că Natsuki va câștiga concursul de frumusețe al festivalului școlii din acest an, nu?
Nu prea știu ce să zic despre asta.
Mie-mi place mai mult de Itsuyo.
A devenit președinta consiliului elevilor imediat cum a fost admisă!
Student Council President
E foarte frumoasă! Și carismatică!
Nu există niciun băiat care să nu se îndrăgostească de ea!
Vreau să fiu legat de ea!
If you wanna talk about popular,
Mutsumi-chan in class C is tops!
She's the latest up-and-coming idol!
Just once, I want to try to talk with her,
even though she rarely comes to school!
Hey, you guys are in the same class
as Natsuki-chan, so support her!
Mutsumi!
Itsuyo!
Oribil.
Văd că ești la fel de
populară ca întotdeauna...
Crezi că vei câștiga?
Nu sunt interesată deloc
de concursul de frumusețe.
Sau mai bine spus,
nu-mi place să atrag atenția...
Evident că nu.
Between the two of you, you'd get
the booby prize in the chest department!
H-Hei! Nu mă atinge acolo!
Haide, nu e ca și cum se vor
micșora dacă mă joc cu ei.
Î-Îmi sângerează nasul...
U-Un demon!
V-Vreau să spun, Akutsu Takuma.
S-S-a întâmplat ceva?
Î-Îmi cer scuze.
Făceam prea multă gălăgie, nu?
Așa că... e-ei bine...
Nu m-ați deranjat sau ceva...
Te rog să mă cruți!
Yamada a căzut pe fereastră!
A câta oară e când se
întâmpla asta astăzi?
There's an ambulance on standby
outside of the main gate.
Ce?
Mai încet!
Don't just stand there yammerin' away to...
Un demon?!
Adică, Akutsu, ai făcut-o din nou?
Înțeleg! Doar am înțeles eu greșit, nu?
Atunci, voi pleca!
Tăcere...
A fost așa de înfricoșător.
Credeam că-i va rupe capul!
That Akuma guy's just having a free for all today.
Crezi că el e vinovatul pentru incidentele în serie cu demoni?
Incidentele în serie cu demoni...
Investigators closing in on a mystery!
Special report - Demonii au apărut în oraș!
Chestiile care tot apar
la știri în ultima vreme?
Un tip purtând o mască de
demon a atacat pietonii!
Cred că el e făptașul.
Se zvonește că se aud mai multe voci venind din casa lui, deși trăiește de unul singur!
Înfiorător!
Natsuki, și tu ar trebui să
stai la distanță de acel tip...
Natsuki, s-a întâmplat ceva?
Nu, totul e în regulă.
E așa un ciudat.
E Demonul Takuma.
Ce carte citește?
Ar trebui
să dispară
pur și simplu
Ar trebui să dispară pur și simplu.
Hei, te poate auzi.
Dar e numai vina lui...
Student Council President
What might all this commotion be?
Student Council President, it's that guy.
It looks like Akuma is causing problems again.
It's the Student Council President!
She's so cool!
Since the school festival is coming up,
I thought it'd be awful if we had
even more problems come up now.
You mustn't do that, Matsumura-san.
Huh?
This is something that can only be corrected by
the student council at that time.
The student council must not be the chain
by which the students are tied down.
For the sake of the students and
the academy, let's all do our best...
Vice President Matsumura.
Ba-dump
Lovely... the Student Council President is just so lovely!
I'm definitely voting for her in the beauty contest!
Besides, I don't think that person is an akuma.
He looks more like a cowardly child.
Scary... Is that an akuma?
He's looking over here!
Let's go so we don't get involved in those incidents.
I'm not an akuma at all, though.
This "Akuma" is Takuma Akutsu, 16,
who was once a normal boy.
Amintire
True, however...
Hey c'mon, let's play dodge ball!
Grădiniță
Speriați
Uh... With you, Akutsu-kun?
Sorry, I'm kinda scared to.
Due to his intimidating air, everyone has been
scared of him since early childhood.
Everyone that approached him was like that.
Școala primară
Why the hell you lookin' at us like that?!
You tryin' to pick a fight, fool?!
As a result, he stopped directly interacting
with others and developed a phobia of humans.
No entry
Do not engage
Stay away
Just like earlier when I stood up a little,
they'd get surprised and fall out of the window.
And even when I want to deny it,
I'm so petrified I can't say anything.
I'm sick of this.
Today's guest is the currently
insanely popular Mutsumi-chan!
You've been so busy lately you don't even
have time to hang out with friends, right?
That isn't true!
Our high school campus festival is coming up soon,
and I've been really looking forward to it!
I promised my friends that I'd
walk around with them there.
About the culture festival, Mutsumi-chan,
will you be in charge of any of the events there?
I don't need any friends.
I sincerely believe that.
As long as I have that one thing, I'm okay.
What I need is...
High School Exams
Complete Preparations in 30 days - Revised edition
Common Questions on the Exam
150 carefully-selected questions
Math Workbook
my studies!
I got this correct.
This is correct, too.
What do we do?
Like I would know...
And these, too.
We should go to the police!
But he's just sitting there.
Correct!
Akuma!
Speriați
Jeez, they almost gave me a heart attack
with all the sudden shouting.
Hello, is this the police?!
There's an Akuma engrossed in
reading his book of spells!
I want to study by myself.
Nothing good comes from
interacting with other people.
This house that my parents left to me
is the only place I can be alone.
Or so I thought...
T...Takuma-kun?
Oh my, welcome home.
Disgraceful!
Ugh, just how many times do you jerks have to
do these disgraceful things before you're satisfied?!
Saotome Natsuki
You pervert!
I-I-I'm leaving now!
Oh my, Takuma-san, let's talk a little more.
S-Student Council President?!
I don't like how stiff that sounds.
Will you call me "Itsuyo"?
Saotome Itsuyo
And don't make that face, either.
Hey!
Wh-what're you doing?! Get away from her!
Aren't you going to get dressed first, Itsuyo?!
It doesn't matter what I'm going to do, does it?
Well, it is inevitable that someone like you with
such a depressing chest would be jealous, though.
The size of my chest has nothing to do with this!
And I'm not jealous of you at all!
Oh? Do you want me to tie you up?
Now's my chance!
Saotome Mutsumi
Ah, no!
I can't do it today! I get so sweaty after a live show!
Oh, Natsuki, you still wear childish ones like that?
I'm so sorry, you two!
How many times must you do these
disgraceful things before you're satisfied?
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, it's Takumatchi! Welcome home!
Saotome Misa
Saotome Yakumo
Sue
Welcome back.
What's up with him?
I don't know.
Right now, this house...
is being controlled by nine women!
They're like demons on an all-out rage fest
that just showed up out of nowhere.
I was completely enjoying my
carefully-crafted life alone,
but now I can't even concentrate on studying.
Since it's come to this, I'm gonna call the police!
Are you saying you want us to leave?
Saotome Futaba
Saotome Kururi
Yo!
Since you allowed us to
so brazenly occupy your home,
if this is what you have decided, we will obey.
We will.
However, what would our dear father say,
were we to return home empty handed as we are?
We are!
You don't have to leave.
Hooray!
Really? Thank goodness.
By the way, why aren't they all
afraid of being around me?
Big Bro Takuma, let's play! Big Bro Takuma?
By the way, why aren't they all
afraid of being around me?
This is too scary!
Concerning the frequent demon incidents,
the police are having a hard time
with their investigation.
They have yet to obtain any clues on the matter.
Pass the soy sauce!
Here you go!
Mutsumi, what about work today?
I'm off.
My, that's rare.
More, please!
Takuma-chan, you haven't even
touched your chopsticks.
Oh, uh...
Sue
I'm afraid of people!
I don't want to associate with other people!
I just want to study by myself!
The entrance exams are next year, you know!
So please, leave my house right now!
I could never say something like that, though.
More, please!
I wonder how I can get them to leave peacefully...
If this keeps up, it will affect
my entrance exam studies...
Has Natsuki-chan piqued your interest?
There's a hole in the wall!
If that's the case...
Why did this happen?
Natsuki-san is always angry and I can't deal with her.
I want to be alone as soon as possible.
What is it?
N-nothing.
Were you always wearing glasses?
Are you making fun of me?
I only wear them when I'm studying.
Glasses are something you wear
when studying, right?
So, they're just for show.
De formă
Do you really hate it that much?
Do you hate studying with me?
Yes! If at all possible, I want to study by myself!
You idiot! Just get on with it!
I will not go along with this!
Itsuyo-chan, you're as aggressive as always!
Don't act like that, Itsuyo.
We all decided on this beforehand.
She's right.
We said that we'd give priority to
raising Natsuki-chan's level.
Itsuyo, cheer up! I'll give you candy later.
More importantly, is Big Brother okay?
He goes on and on about studying,
and I don't feel he's motivated to do
the most crucial thing.
Oh really?
I totally get it.
He's completely unmotivated by that.
You need to show some motivation too!
I'm not worried about anything in regards to that.
After all, Takuma-san is the man
that our father approves of.
I'm so nervous I can't concentrate on studying.
Calm down... I need to calm down.
I have to focus more. Focus...
FOCUS!
Of all places, that's where it chooses to go...
What do I do?
What is the meaning of this?
I even put on glasses like Dad said to, but...
Matematică A2
Clasa: 2-D   Nume: Saotome Natsuki
I don't understand this problem at all!
And what on earth is up with math?
Do I really need this type of thing?
Trig...Trigonometric function?
Is that some sort of esoteric technique?
Disgraceful!
I'b shorry!
I was trying to get my eraser...
Are you seriously even motivated to do this?!
I am.
I promised my deceased mother.
I said I'd study... and become...
become a respectable person.
Are the two of you just about done studying?
Come and take a little break.
Why is this happening again...
I accidentally forgot to buy toilet paper,
so I'd like you two to go get some.
Oh right, when you do this,
you must hold hands and go shopping.
Make sure you don't forget, okay?
I want to go home now.
This is a notice to all residents of the neighborhood.
There have been many dangerous incidents
occurring around this area.
Please refrain from going out at night.
You know they suspect that you're the culprit
in the akuma incidents, right?
Huh?
It's because they see an incident in the classroom,
and you let everyone continue to misunderstand it.
Why don't you even try to defend yourself.
It'd be pointless to do that.
My face is scary and my body is big.
I only cause problems, so I can't do anything
about being treated like a criminal.
Is she angry?!
Speaking of the akuma incidents,
they were right around here, right?
And the place where you saved my life...
Yeah... it was.
Seeing you right now, I get annoyed.
I-I'm sorry.
Even though back then,
you were... so cool.
An akuma!
What is that?
Is this for TV?
It disappeared?
It seems they've safely deployed the barrier.
It's huge!
This summon brought a much stronger one
compared to the previous ones.
Does this mean that Father's oracle
is one hundred percent true?
Huh? What do we do?
It doesn't look like Natsuki can
defeat it at her current level,
but we have to believe in her.
You can do it, Natsuki-chan, Takuma-kun.
This is definitely a Hrugnir!
I can't believe such a high-level
demon was summoned!
I can't buy us any extra time for the barrier!
What do I do?
I'll lose the opportunity to raise my level
if I hold hands and shop.
Then, we have to do it the other way...
It's impossible to get rid of this akuma!
Let's just run for it!
What a loathsome thing to say at a time like this.
That's really the type of man he is.
Find somewhere and take cover!
Okay!
I really hate him.
Hey, get ahold of yourself! Hey!
You protected me? Why?
Știam eu
I knew it.
Nothing good comes from
being involved with other people.
Nu iese nimic bun
din interacțiunea
cu alți oameni
I'm okay with being alone my whole life.
I wholeheartedly believe that.
Yay! C'mon, this way!
Wait!
And yet...
My body had moved before I realized it.
This is how you really are.
Nothing's changed at all.
Natsuki-san, get out of here and get someone to help!
I can't.
That demon can't be defeated by humans.
This is my first time...
So... be gentle with me.
"Hold hands and go shopping," cancelled.
Țineți-vă de mână și mergeți la magazin
Failed
Val x Love "Massage chest" complete.
Entering experience points.
Siegrune level up confirmed,
and "Kiss with a Lover" acknowledged.
Valkyrie, invoked.
As told in the myths,
in Asgard's Valhalla, there live
goddesses called Valkyries.
Natsuki-san...
Valkyries grow stronger as long as they are in love.
The reason being that, love is...
the source of a maiden's power.
Bun! S-au descurcat destul de bine!
Da.
Asta e grozav, Itsuyo!
Of course they'd be able to do at least that.
Ai văzut asta?
Takuma dă tot ce poate.
Why don't you give it up
and show your face around here,
Soră mai mare Ichika?
Hmpf, 320 de secunde.
Dacă de atât are nevoie
ca să elimine un demon,
atunci, spiritul său e mult prea slab.
Nu aș putea recunoaște niciodată o asemenea persoană ca iubitul nostru.
Currently, this world is in grave danger of destruction.
Brave young man,
you should surely understand this personally now.
At this rate, in not even a few days' time,
this world will be enveloped in flame.
This world, this land of Midgard...
I want you to protect it from the akuma's grasp.
Who are you?
I am Odin, ruler of the gods of Asgard.
You will need a sword to win this battle.
I will bestow one upon you.
There are nine sacred swords.
The nine beautiful, young Valkyries.
As long as a Valkyrie is in love,
she will grow stronger.
You will become the Valkyries' lover.
A II-a fiică: Futaba
„Gerhilde”
Castel: Nivel 12
I fiică: Ichika
„Brunhilde”
Lance: Nivel 1
A III-a fiică: Misa
„Ortlinde”
Sfoară: Nivel 6
You will fall in love with them.
A IV-a fiică: Shino
„Waltraute”
Armură: Nivel 2
Grow, and refine yourself.
A VI-a fiică: Mutsumi
„Helmwige”
Aripi: Nivel 5
A V-a fiică: Itsuyo
„Shwertleite”
Lanț: Nivel 5
A IX-a fiică: Kururi
„Rossweisse”
Tun: Nivel 9
You must show proof...
A VIII-a fiică: Yakumo
„Grimgerde”
Sunet: Nivel 4
A VII-a fiică: Natsuki
„Siegrune”
Sabie: Nivel 20
Love is what will save the world!
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
If we don't understand love,
you & I won't get anywhere, you know?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
Vrem să-ți împărțim inima!
(How do you tell me?)
Input sweet nothings
Failed - Cancelled - They don't resonate at all
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch me and bring me one
Successful - Complete - Isn't cutting-edge tech great?
(Hold me tight)
Why won't you say romance?
Let's bring it to love
Get more experience and level up my maiden heart
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
I'll teach you that love is a maiden's power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Nine times out of ten, they're surely already lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Fluttering in my chest, dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Your shy akuma mind, kiss for you!
Will completely change, kiss for me!
Let's begin our romance!
We managed to defeat the akuma
this time around, but to fight well,
it's important to raise our levels higher than normal
so this won't happen again.
Okay. The Val Love sure have a lot of different levels.
What does that mean? Do you have
some sort of objection to being our lovers?
Not at all! I'm just wondering why I was chosen.
The ruler of the gods of Asgard, who's my papa...
my Father, accepted you as the one.
In any case, as our lover Einherjar,
you will raise the levels of my sisters and I.
And if we don't kiss you to start with,
we cannot manifest the true power of the Valkyries.
Simt cum stomacul mi
zdrobește de la presiune...
Data viitoare: Fata cu lanțul.
Data
viitoare
Fata cu lanțul